let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question:
      "What is the correct way to read a string from the console in C#?",
    answer: "Console.ReadLine();",
    options: [
      "input(&#x22;Enter a string: &#x22;);",
      "Console.ReadLine();",
      "cin >> myVar;",
      "scanf(&#x22;%s&#x22;, &myVar);",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 2,
    question:
      "What is the correct way to calculate the square root of a number in C#?",
    answer: "Math.Sqrt(myNumber);",
    options: [
      "sqrt(myNumber);",
      "myNumber.sqrt();",
      "Math.Sqrt(myNumber);",
      "Math.sqrt(myNumber);",
    ],
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question:
      "What is the result of the following C# expression: !true && false || true",
    answer: "true",
    options: ["true", "false", "0", "1"],
  },
  {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is the result of the expression !true in C#?",
    answer: "false",
    options: ["true", "false", "0", "1"],
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "What is the correct way to concatenate two strings in C#?",
    answer: "myString + yourString;",
    options: [
      "myString + yourString;",
      "myString.Concat(yourString);",
      "myString & yourString;",
      "myString.Append(yourString);",
    ],
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....
  {
    numb: 6,
    question:
      "What is the result of the following expression in C#: (int) 3.14?",
    answer: "3",
    options: ["3.14", "3", "3.0", "4"],
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question:
      "What is the result of the following expression in C#: 4 + 5 * 6?",
    answer: "30",
    options: ["24", "26", "34", "30"],
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question:
      "What is the result of the following expression in C#: &#x22;Hello&#x22;.Length?",
    answer: "5",
    options: ["5", "Hello", "H", "&#x22;Hello&#x22;"],
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "What is the result of the expression true && false in C#?",
    answer: "false",
    options: ["true", "false", "0", "1"],
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question:
      "What is the correct way to read an integer from the console in C#?",
    answer: "int.Parse(Console.ReadLine());",
    options: [
      "Console.readInt();",
      "System.in.readInt();",
      "cin >> myInt;",
      "int.Parse(Console.ReadLine());",
    ],
  },
];
